shoofo.com 2010-11-29

# Shoofo Privacy Policy

**Privacy notice.**

Shoofo is committed to protecting your privacy and will collect no personal information about you unless you choose to provide that information to us. 

Our website automatically logs visitor information from which summary statistics are created. We use the summary statistics to help us make our site more useful to visitors, such as assessing what information is of most and least interest to visitors, and for other purposes such as determining the site's technical design specifications and identifying system performance or problem areas. 

The following are representative of the types of information automatically collected and stored about your visit: 

  * the Internet domain and Internet Protocol (IP) address from which you access our Web site; 
  * the type of Internet browser and the operating system of the computer you use to access our site; 
  * the date and time you visit our site; 
  * the pages you visit on our site; 
  * if you linked to our Web site from another Web site, the address of that Web site; and, if you linked to our Web site from a search Web site, the address of that Web site and the search term you used. 

We will never sell or distribute any your personal information to any third-party for any reason. 

Please see our payment processor's Privacy Policy concerning collected information. 

Copyright notice. 

All materials on this web site are copyrighted with all rights reserved. No image of this site may be reproduced without written permission. No part of this site may be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise used for any commercial purposes. You may not frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) of ours. You may not use any meta tags or any other "hidden text" utilizing any of our trade names or trademarks without our permission in writing. Any unauthorized use terminates the permission or license to access this site. Spidering (automatic retrieving the entire site or parts of it with a specific program) is forbidden. Searching our servers for unpublished or offline files is forbidden too. 

If you have any questions or comments about the information presented here, please contact our support-team at sales@shoofo.com
